And over here, as you see, we have Gemini.google.com.
So this is the actual chatbot.
If I click on the link, I'll be referred to the app, as you see.
And it says, "Nano Banana Pro is now on Gemini 3 Pro."
Yep.
So if I wait a little bit, as you see, it says, "Hello, Nemo."
So I didn't even need to sign in or do anything related,
because I'm already signed in with my Gmail account, you see?
So it's very compatible, as I said, with other products of Google,
that I don't even need to log in.
It's logged in already, you know?
And the "Nano Banana" thing that you see over here,
as you see, it also says, "Create Image" over here
with a banana emoji.
So the banana thing is about image creation of Gemini, you know?
That is also another thing that we're going to be talking about
in this very lesson.
But let's get started with asking Gemini something, right?
So we also have add files over here, as you see,
photos, add from drive, and upload files.
And we also can have tools, as you see.
So we have deep research, we have create image, canvas,
guided learning, and dynamic view, right?
And we also can choose our model, it says, "Fast."
So in answer quickly, or thinking with three pro,
we'll take a little bit of time to answer your questions,
but we'll be more deep, you know, when it comes to answering.
So we can also use these keywords, as you see over here.
It has deep research, learn, build, and write.